[{"answer": "Not yet.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "What are you looking at?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "Very, very well.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "Dr. Oz, how are you?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "Well, resolutions actually do make a difference.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "What is the best advice for people to get to January and think New Year, new me, new start?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "Well, we have made it easy to do the wrong thing in America.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "What are the things about the American diet, the way of life, whatever it may be, that are particular, perhaps, to America?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "Just from French fries.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "Just from French fries?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "It would dramatically change our life expectancy, but, more importantly, the quality of our life.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "If everybody just exercised better portion control, literally cut the amount they ate by, say, a third, what effect would that have on the average life?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "It's a huge benefit for the country.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "Is it good for America that you have a first lady and president who are obviously very physically fit themselves?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "It's a perfect amount.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "If you walked as an adult for half an hour a day -- you know, I walk here across Central Park, say, to CNN, and I feel like it's a pretty good exercise if you walk at a reasonable pace, is that enough to be fit?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "Well, we're going to --", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "Well, I'm basically in perfect physical (INAUDIBLE)?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "If I could figure it out, I'd fix it.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "Why do you think you've had a -- a battle with your weight?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "I don't.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "You don't know what it is?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "Sure, plenty of times.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "Did you ever get help for it?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "I eat too much.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 194, "question": "Where do you -- where do you fall down in terms of dealing with it?", "qSentId": 193}, {"answer": "I think they should have the -- the flu shot, without question.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "Should they have the jab?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "What we ought to, I think, crave, is hope.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "What is the best advice, if there is any, for people who get caught up in these terrible tragedies, about how to somehow get back?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Because I can't tell you how many times we've lost one couple, a long married couple, and then soon after, we'll lose the spouse.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "How do you deal with that particular kind of stress, a really -- like a death in the family, a death of a close friend, even, for some people, a death of a beloved pet?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "There is no question at all that broken hearts exist and they kill people.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "Does that -- does it exist in medical terms, a broken heart?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "Rhodiola.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "Rhodiola?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "Are you basically telling me you've been half cut on vodka your entire career?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Cannabis, a fascinating story, in part because there is no question there's medicinal benefit.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "Can we add a few, you know, cannabis joints to the equation now that they're legal in some states?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "It's addictive as cigarettes, in my opinion.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "ORGAN: How addictive is cannabis?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "It does -- it has more dangers in part because when you're under the influence of cannabis, your judgment is a bit more affected than it would be under cigarettes.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "Is it more dangerous than cigarettes?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "There are a couple of problems with cannabis.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "But if you, as one of America's topmost renowned doctors, says it's not more dangerous than cigarettes, surely, it should just be legalized, then, right, like cigarettes?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "Well, the body mass index is -- it's in the overweight category, but I'm not that worried about that.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "But how -- how bad is that, the mass index?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "Half of your height, half of 73 inches, which is 36 and a half inches.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "What should my waist be?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "Well, ideally it would be less than 140.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "How bad is that?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "Thirty-seven.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "What's mine?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "The best way to do it is to get that waist size down to 36 and a half inches.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "I need more healthy cholesterol -- how do I get more healthy cholesterol?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "Uh, there are a couple of little tips.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "What's the best way to do that?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "But can I share that for a second?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "It's supposed to be, ideally, about 115 over 75, ideally.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "How high?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Z: Exercise.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "And what causes that kind of thing?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "Well, the -- the number one thing that folks ought to start doing is to automate their lives so the easy decisions are the right ones and are -- and are easier to make.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "So what should I be doing to deal with this?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "Coffee itself is fine, because it's a -- it's the number one source of antioxidants in America.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "Is that bad for me?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "You could dramatically change these numbers in six weeks.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "-- I'm going to get you back in -- how -- how long would I need to try and really deal with this?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "Well, it's -- it's a combination.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 641, "question": "Or is it just luck?", "qSentId": 640}, {"answer": "That's a great question.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 683, "question": "So my question to you is, is there a preventative measure that I could use to help alleviate the pain so that, long-term, it won't turn into arthritis?", "qSentId": 682}, {"answer": "You know, we tackle this on the show a lot because there's actually 116 million Americans with chronic pain issues.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 686, "question": "What is the best way to try and deal with it?", "qSentId": 685}, {"answer": "It turns out that about two thirds of how long you live is based on your lifestyle.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 718, "question": "And what's the balance between genetics and just good living?", "qSentId": 717}, {"answer": "Good diet.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 762, "question": "What is the secret to long life, do you think, in terms of health?", "qSentId": 761}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 768, "question": "Do what in bed?", "qSentId": 767}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 773, "question": "Mimi -- Mimi, let me ask you, have you ever some kind?", "qSentId": 772}, {"answer": "Milk.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 781, "question": "Do you drink alcohol?", "qSentId": 780}, {"answer": "It's obviously worked.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 788, "question": "What about that for a recipe for long life?", "qSentId": 787}, {"answer": "The -- the number one under appreciated health problem in America is sleep issues.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 812, "question": "And if you can't get enough, what do you do about it?", "qSentId": 811}, {"answer": "It -- it completely disrupts sleep patterns, and for one very important reason.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 841, "question": "It can't help you sleep, does it?", "qSentId": 840}, {"answer": "You cannot get the flu from the flu shot because the material is -- is actually dead flu virus.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 863, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 862}, {"answer": "This is literally the biggest needle I could find.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 874, "question": "You're enjoying this, aren't you?", "qSentId": 873}, {"answer": "It's recommended that after the age of six months, that we give it to our kids.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 898, "question": "Should children have them?", "qSentId": 897}, {"answer": "You know, mental is where you win it all.", "docId": "130111pmt", "aSentId": 923, "question": "How much of it is mental in the end?", "qSentId": 922}]